# **OKORO GODWIN CHINEDU**

16, ABATA CLOSE SARI IGAMMU Lagos State

EMAIL: <a href="mailto:chinedugodwin300@yahoo.com">chinedugodwin300@yahoo.com</a>
Website: <a href="https://portfolio-cv-zuri.netlify.app">https://portfolio-cv-zuri.netlify.app</a>

Tel: 08062850763

### PERSONAL DATA.

TIMIA

Nationality: Nigerian
Date of Birth: 25<sup>th</sup> Jan 1991

State of Origin: Abia

Local Government Area: Arochukwu

Marital Status: Single Gender: Male

Religion: Christianity

### **CAREER SUMMARY**

A statistical analyst and a Market Research Analyst, professional I.T personnel and frontend web designer with a certification from (freecodecamp.org), Online conducting/sales Admin expert with a certificate from GOOGLE, recently took an Android course with GOOGLE AFRICA DEVELOPER SCHOLARSHIP in conjunction with ANDELA and PLURALSIGHT which will earn me a certification in Android and currently working with Outcess Solution as a Software developer and Microsoft Azure Developer.

## **SKILL/KEY ATTRIBUTES**

- ➤ Organizational, leadership and project management skill demonstrated in dominion leadership instituted.
- ➤ Excellent technical skills and practical experience on information and communication technology.
- ➤ Analytical skill coupled with various I.T diploma degrees.
- ➤ Good presentational and mass communication skills demonstrated during my NYSC year in kebbi state on cleaning and personal hygiene.
- ➤ Knowledgeable on computer programming with an ongoing course on PluralSight.
- ➤ Online conducting/sales Admin expert with a certificate from GOOGLE as a Digital Marketer.

# WORKING EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2018

	JUMIA	2010 - 2010
	Active work as an online sales Administrator.	
(	o Intensive training on sales delivering, consulting,	
	Customer care and all round sales.	
$\triangleright$	Federal Government college	2018 - 2019
	<ul> <li>Economics, Computer science and I.T personnel</li> </ul>	
$\triangleright$	Starlight college	2019 - 2020
	<ul> <li>Economics, Computer science and I.T personnel</li> </ul>	
	Outcess Solution	2021 – date

# **EDUCATIONAL**

Abia state university uturu abia State	2010 - 2014
B.sc (Hons) in statistics (Second Class Division)	
Great trinity college kirikiri town Lagos	2001 - 2007
West African Senior School Certificate	
Diamond international school Lagos	1995 - 2001
First School Leaving Testimonial	
National youth service corps -	2018 - 2019

### **OTHER CERTIFICATION**

- Front End Responsive web Designer (freecodecamp.org) 2019
- ➤ D.L.I (dominion leadership institute) 2012
- ➤ (Diploma) IT information technology 2013
- ➤ (Diploma) Business computing 2018
- ➤ SOLO LEARN certificates in (HTML, CSS, PHP, JAVA SRICPT, SQL)
- ➤ Google Digital Marketing 2019

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Web designer, Computer skills, Computer fundamentals, internet applications, Microsoft office word, Microsoft office 365, Excel, Microsoft office, Power point, networking software And Pc Maintenances.

#### REFEREES

Dr. Ogbonnaya Nkwola Nigeria Police Headquarters Abuja 08163253632

Mrs. Akunna Onyenaucheya Niger Delta University Teaching Hospital (NDUTH) Okolobiri Bayelsa State. 08030580070